ILGWU. Charles Zimmerman Collection of Radical Pamphlets 5780/178
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Herbert Solow; Samuel S. White; Travers Clements. Union-smashing in Sacramento, the truth about the criminal syncicalism trial, by Herbert Solow, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  With prefatory notes by Sameul S. White and Travers Clements.
- Daniel De Leon; William H. Berry. De Leon-Berry debate on solution of the trust problem, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 98)
  University Extension Society, Philadelphia, January 27, 1913
- Some facts on women's wages in New York State, 1936 (Box 9, Folder 99)
- Henry Somerville. Why the guilds decayed, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 100)
- Agustin Souchy. The tragic week in May, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 101)
- Boris Souvarine. The Third International, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 102)
- Needle Trades Bazaar Souvenir Journal: sixteen months of life and struggle in the Needle Trades Workers Industrial Union. (Box 9, Folder 103)
- Maksim Maksimovich Litvinov; M. Lunacharsky. The Soviet's fight for disarmament, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 104)
  Speeches by M. Litvinov at Geneva, 1932, and other documents in sequel to "The Soviet union and peace", with an introduction by M. Lunacharsky.
- AFL (American Federation of Labor). Soviet imperialism plunders Asia, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 105)
- Soviet Russia arrests Henryk Ehrlich and Victor Alter, noted Polish Socialist leaders, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 106)
- The Soviet Satellites: 1. Terror east of the Elbe, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 107)
- Harry Gannes; G. Marion. Spain Defends Democracy, 1936 (Box 9, Folder 108)
- John Spargo. A memorandum on trade with Soviet Russia, 1921 (Box 9, Folder 109)
  Submitted to the Committee on Foreign Relations of the United States Senate, January, 1921, in connection with the hearing upon the resolution of the Hon. Joseph I. France, relating to the resumption of trade with Soviet Russia. By John Spargo.
- George Spiro; Moissaye J. Olgin. Paris on the barricades, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 110)
  Story of the immortal struggle of the Communards of 1871 for the first workers government, heroically reared by the working class, and crushed by the bloody hand of the bourgeoisie. With an introduction by Moissaye J. Olgin.
- Robert G. Spivack. The lesson of Czechoslovakia., 1938 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Philip Spratt. The Communist "peace" appeal; its real character., 1951 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Joseph Stalin. The theory and practice of Leninism, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Joseph Stalin. The foundations of Leninism, 1932-1934 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  10th anniversary edition
- Joseph Stalin. Interviews with foreign workers' delegations, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Joseph Stalin. New conditions, new tasks, 1931 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  Speech delivered at the Conference of Leaders of Industry, June 23, 1931
- Joseph Stalin. The Soviets and the individual, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Joseph Stalin; Roy Wilson Howard. The Stalin-Howard interview, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Joseph Stalin. Stalin on the new Soviet constitution, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Joseph Stalin. Stalin Reports: The world situation, the internal and international position of the Soviet Union, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Joseph Stalin. The war of national liberation, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Joseph Stalin. The war of national liberation. II, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Private Attorneys-General: Group Action in the Fight for Civil Liberties, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  Reprinted from The Yale Law Journal
- Jan Stanczyk. Rights for Jews in new Poland, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  Declaration of the Polish government-in-exile, presented to the Jewish labor committee by Mr. Jan Stanczyk
- Emanuel Stein; Carl Raushenbush; Lois MacDonald. Labor and the new deal, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- I. N. Steinberg. Unpromised land, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Stephen Leacock. Stephen Leacock's plan to relieve the depression in 6 days, to remove it in 6 months, to eradicate it in 6 years., 1933 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- David Kilburn Stevens; Peter W. Dykema; Martha Powell Setchell. Sing! The all-purpose song book for home; school; community choruses; social meetings and festivities., 1938 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  With complete piano accompaniment. Compiled and edited by David Stevens and Peter W. Dykema; decorations by Martha Powell Setchell.
- Maxwell S. Stewart. Debts: good or bad?, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Maxwell S. Stewart. The Negro in America, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Ray Stewart. War in China, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- The Story of the Abraham Lincoln Battalion: written in the trenches of Spain., 1937 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Souvenir Journal: brief history of Needle Trades Workers Indusrtrial Union. (Box 10, Folder 23)
  English and Yiddish
- The story of the sea (Box 10, Folder 24)
- John Strachey. Why fascism leads to war, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Twentieth Century Fund. Strikes and democratic government, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Seafarers' International Union of North America. Strikes and strike strategy, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Anna Louise Strong. The Soviet Union and World Peace: Disarmament, Non-Aggression, The Far East, League of Nations, Franco-Soviet Pact., 1935 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Communist International. The struggle against imperialist war and the tasks of communists, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  Resolution of the Sixth World Congress of the Communist International, 1928 / reprinted by the Marxist-Leninist Organizing Committee.
- Los Sucesos de mayo en Barcelona: (relato autentico), 1937 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Survey; a journal of Soviet and East European studies. Russia and Germany, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- American Jewish Congress. Survey and outlook: a report on the American Jewish Congress, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  Submitted by the Executive Director to the Biennial National Convention, November 7-9, 1953, New York City.
- W. B. Sutch. New Zealand's labor government at work, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Romuald Szumski. Labor and the Soviet system, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- The tactics of disruption: communist methods exposed., 1949 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Tampa: tar and terror., 1935 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Ten good reasons: for cracking the quota system in American education. (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Joseph Tenenbaum. The economic crisis of the third reich, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- J. William Terry. American labor and the trade agreements, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Communist International. Theses and statutes of the third (Communist) International, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  Adopted by the second congress July 17th-August 7th, 1920.
- Communist Party of the U.S.A. Thesis and resolutions for the seventh National Convention of the Communist party of U.S.A., 1930 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  Central Committee plenum, March 31-April 4, 1930.
- Communist International. The theses and statutes of the Communist International, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  adopted at the Second World Congress, July 17 to August 7, 1920, Moscow, Russia.
- William Ernest Hocking. They fought Hitler first, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  Report on the treatment of German anti-Nazis in concentration camps from 1933 to 1939, based on contemporary records. With an introduction by William Ernest Hocking.
- RILU (Red International of Labor Unions). Resolutions and Decisions: Third World Congress of the Red International of Labor Unions, 1924 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  Moscow, July, 1924: resolutions and decisions
- This is our home. 1. The American Pattern, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- This is our home. 2. The New World and the Old, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- This is our home. 3. Prelude to Freedom, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- This is our home. 4. Group Life in America, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- This is our home. 5. The Hands of Esau, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Norman Thomas. Democratic socialism, a new appraisal., 1953 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- Norman Thomas. The plight of the share-cropper, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  Includes Report of survey made by the Memphis chapter, L. I. D. and the Tyronza socialist party under the direction of William R. Amberson.
- United States Congress Against War and Fascism. Third United States Congress against War and Fascism, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  Program, January 3, 4, 5, 1936, public auditorium, Cleveland, Ohio.
- Virginia Thompson; Richard Adloff; Blair Bolles. Empire's end in southeast Asia [by] Virginia Thompson and Richard Adloff. U. S. policy in southeast Asia [by] Blair Bolles., 1949 (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Maurice Thorez. France of the People's front and its mission in the world, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Maurice Thorez. The unity of the French nation, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Russia Today Society (London, England). Through workers' eyes: Report of the American Workers Delegation to Soviet Russia., 1931 (Box 10, Folder 52)
- John Q. Tilson. The embargo on Spain, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 53)
- Anti-Discrimination Department. The time is now: report of activities, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 54)
- Thomas Tippett. Mill shadows: a drama of social forces in four acts, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 55)
- Josip Broz Tito. Workers manage factories in Yugoslavia, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 56)
- Abraham Joel Tobias. Substandard wages: an analysis of their extent and effect, and what must be done to establish a higher wage level, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  Design and presentation by Abraham Joel Tobias; prepared in cooperation with Textile Workers Union of America, CIO.
- Today's fight against the bosses: expropriate the war industries., 1941 (Box 10, Folder 58)
- Ralph De Toledano. How communism demoralizes youth, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 59)
- Lewis Paul Todd. The Marshall plan; a program of international cooperation, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  Prepared for the Advisory Committee on Education, Economic Cooperation Administration.
- American Workers Party. Toward an American revolutionary labor movement: statement of programmatic orientation, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 61)
- Young Communist League. Towards a mass Young Communist League, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  Resolutions adopted by the July Plenum of the Young Communist League, U.S.A.
- Communist Party of the U.S.A. Toward revolutionary mass work, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 63)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor). The A.F. of L. at work towards democracy in Germany: the voices of free German labor, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 64)
- Labour Party (Great Britain). Towards world plenty, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 65)
- Eugene V. Debs; Alexander Trachtenber. The heritage of Gene Debs, selections, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  100th Anniversary edition. Critical introd. by Alexander Trachtenberg.
- ILP (Independent Labour Party). Trade unions in Soviet Russia, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  A collection of Russian trade union documents compiled by the I. L. P. Information committee and the International section of the Labour research department.
- TUC (Trades Union Congress). Trade union structure and closer unity, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 68)
- TUC (Trades Union Congress). Trade Unions and the War Situation, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 69)
- TUC (Trades Union Congress). Trade unionism in central Europe; T.U.C. survey., 1945 (Box 10, Folder 70)
- John Dewey; Roger N. Baldwin; Christopher Emmet. Tragedy of a people, racialism in Czecho-Slovakia, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  With an appeal by John Dewey, Roger N. Baldwin, Christopher Emmet ... and others.
- A tribute to William Green, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 72)
- Leon Trotsky; Max Shachtman. In defense of the Soviet Union, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  Introduction by Max Shachtman.
- Leon Trotsky; H. N. Brailsford. The defence of terrorism (Terrorism and communism) a reply to Karl Kautsky, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  Preface by H.N. Brailsford.
- Leon Trotsky. The first five years of the Communist International, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 75)
- Leon Trotsky. From October to Brest-Litovsk, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 76)
- Leon Trotsky. Germany: the key to the international situation, 1931 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  Introduction by Ted Grant.
- Leon Trotsky. I stake my life, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  Trotsky's address to the N.Y. Hippodrome meeting.
- Leon Trotsky; J. G. Wright. The Kirov assassination, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  Translated by J. G. Wright.
- Leon Trotsky. The Revolution in Spain, 1931 (Box 10, Folder 80)
- Leon Trotsky. Stalinism and bolshevism; concerning the historical and theoretical roots of the Fourth International, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 81)
- Leon Trotsky; Max Shachtman. The strategy of the world revolution, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  Translated with an introduction by Max Shachtman.
- Report of court proceedings, the case of the Trotskyite-Zinovievite terrorist centre, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  Heard before the Military collegium of the Supreme court of the U.S.S.R., Moscow, August 19-24, 1936, in re G. E. Zinoviev, L. B. Kamenev, G. E. Evdokimov, I. N. Smirnov, I. P. Bakayev, V. A. Ter-Vaganyan, S. V. Mrachkovsky, E. A. Dreitzer, E. S. Holtzman
- Walter Trumbull. Life in the U. S. Army (Box 10, Folder 84)
- Philip Murray. The truth about contributory and non-contributory pensions and social insurance, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 85)
- The truth crushes commie lies: American unions work with the United States Department of Labor in giving workers from other lands the truth about free labor., 1951 (Box 10, Folder 86)
- S. Tsirul. The practice of Bolshevik self-criticism: how the American Communist Party carries out self-criticism and controls fulfillment of decisions, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 87)
- Political education. Part 1 the two worlds., 1934 (Box 10, Folder 88)
- TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America). TWUA Speakers Manual (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Gus Tyler. Section 501 (a) and the proper functions of unions, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Socialist Party (U.S.). Unions face the Depression., 1938 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Vernon Bartlett. Unknown Europe, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  Foreword by Vernon Bartlett.
- Samuel Untermyer. Civilization's only weapon against Hitlerism, 1934 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  Address of Mr. Samuel Untermyer, read at the Testimonial Dinner to Mr. William Green at the Aldine Club New York City, February 14, 1934.
- Inter-Union Institute for Labor and Democracy. U.S. labor policy at the fork of the road; documentary report on the conflict in the Congress over labor policy., 1946 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Samuel Van Valkenburg. Pacific Asia; a political atlas., 1947 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Manuel Antonio de Varona Loredo. The drama of Cuba before America, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Veritas. Pro-war communism!, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Harold G. Vatter. Victory through unionism (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Charles Vincent. The Popular Front in France: a short history of the French working class from 1934 to 1938 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Carl Hermann Voss. Answers on the Palestine question, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  3rd edition, revised and enlarged
- Andrey Yanuaryevich Vyshinsky. On condemning the preparation of a new war and concluding a five-power pact for the strengthening peace, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  Speeches at the fourth session of the United Nations General Assembly, November, 1949.
- Andrey Yanuaryevich Vyshinsky. Speeches by A.Y. Vyshinsky on measures against the threat of another war and for strengthening peace and friendship among nations, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  Delivered at the Plenary meetings of the sixth session of the United Nations General Assembly, Nov. 8, 1951 and Nov. 16, 1951.
- Wage Committee report (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Lowell Wakefield. Hitler's spy plot in the U. S. A., 1939 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Tom Walsh. What is this Shop Stewards' Movement? (Box 11, Folder 17)
- General Mills. War work: a daybook for the home., 1942 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Harry F. Ward. Concerted Action for Peace, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Harold Ward. National defense for whom?, 1935 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Harry Waton. The Marxist; an aid to the study of capital, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Harry Waton. Natural dialectics of proletarian internationals and parties, and New Communist manifesto, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Harry Waton. Nature and historic function of socialism and communism (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Harry Waton. The Ninth thermidor of the Russian Revolution (the historic significance of the Trotzkyite Trial) (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Harry Waton. The philosophy of Marx., 1921 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Harry Waton. Spain and France on the Crossroads, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Harry Waton. War and peace: what peace after the war?, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Position of the R.I.L.U. sections and their role in the leadership of the economic struggles and unemployed movement (Box 11, Folder 28)
  Theses adopted by the Eighth Session of the Central Council of the R.I.L.U.
- M. J. Olgin. The way out, a program for American labor, 1934 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  Manifesto and principal resolutions adopted by the eighth convention of the Communist Party of the U.S.A., held in Cleveland, Ohio, April 2-8, 1934. Introduction by M.J. Olgin.
- International Fur and Leather Workers Union. We ask justice for our union leaders!, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- William Weinstone. The great sit-down strike, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Albert Weisbord. Passaic: the story of a struggle against starvation wages and for the right to organize, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Mac Weiss. "In Flanders field..."., 1935 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Max Weiss. Happy days for American youth, 1935 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- BSEIU (Building Service Employees International Union). Welcome! (Box 11, Folder 35)
- United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union. Welcome new member: you have joined the only International Union exclusively composed of Cement, Lime, Gypsum and Allied Industries Workers. (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Western New York Trade Union Directory and Manual, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor). What can I do about it? (Box 11, Folder 38)
- What happened to the trade unions behind the Iron Curtain, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- What the I.L.D. does for labor: defense, relief, legislation, education. (Box 11, Folder 40)
- What to Do When the Rabble-Rouser Comes to Town (Box 11, Folder 41)
- What will happen with Germany? The creation of the National Committee Free Germany: the manifesto and its significance. (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Abraham John Muste. What would pacifists have done about Hitler? A discussion of war, dictators, and pacifism, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 43)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor). When you have a case before a regional labor board., 1934 (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Basil A. Wheeler; Edward Thimme. The problem of the hour, 1932 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  Introduction to the Consumer Party by Edward Thimme.
- Communist Party of Great Britain. Where is Trotsky going?, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 46)
- James T. Farrell. Who are the 18 prisoners in the Minneapolis Labor Case? How the Smith "Gag" Act has endangered workers rights and free speech, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  Foreword by James T. Farrell.
- AFL (American Federation of Labor). Who is the imperialist?, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 48)
- Joseph Clark. Who are the Young Communists?, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 49)
- Arturo Giovannitti; John Dos Passos. Who killed Carlo Tresca?, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  Forewords by Arturo Giovannitti [and] John Dos Passos.
- Why every worker should join the Communist Party., 1930 (Box 11, Folder 51)
- Why this election sample ballot (Box 11, Folder 52)
- Why are Jews persecuted for their religion? (Box 11, Folder 53)
- Independent Labor League of America. Why? a labor party., 1935 (Box 11, Folder 54)
- Why unions?, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 55)
- UE (United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America.). When you come back: UE's orientation handbook for returning servicemen., 1945 (Box 11, Folder 56)
- Why you should vote Communist: what are the real issues in this election?: which party is your party?: for what candidates shall you vote?: what can you expect of this election?, 1934 (Box 11, Folder 57)
- Roy Wilkins. "Rape"; a case history of murder, terror and injustice visited upon a negro community, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 58)
- International Labour Conference. The world of industry and labour, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  Report of the director to the twenty-fifth session of the International Labour Conference, June 1939.
- Wisdom, Justice and Moderation: The Case of Angelo Herndon., 1935 (Box 11, Folder 60)
- Herman Wolf. Labor defends America, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 61)
- Bertram David. Wolfe. Science joins the party, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 62)
- Bertram David Wolfe. Things we want to know, 1934 (Box 11, Folder 63)
- Bertram David Wolfe. What is the communist opposition?, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 64)
- Matthew Woll. Steps necessary for high postwar employment, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 65)
- Abner E. Woodruff. The evolution of industrial democracy, 1914 (Box 11, Folder 66)
- Work Book A (Box 11, Folder 67)
  Federal Text Book
- Work Book B (Box 11, Folder 67)
- The Worker's Bank Limited Tel-Aviv, Israel., 1932 (Box 11, Folder 68)
- United States Department of Labor. Workers and national defense, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 69)
- National Labor Service. Working for labor: the story of the National Labor Service, founded to promote good will among American workers of all races and religions. (Box 11, Folder 70)
- Romain Rolland. The World Congress Against War: report on the congress, 1932 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  Opening address by Romain Rolland; and the manifesto adopted at Amsterdam, August 27-29, 1932.
- The World cries out, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  Statements by leading individuals, organizations and newspapers worldwide on Germany's treatment of Jews written during the Nazi regime.
- E. Clark Worman. Facts about labor leaders, worker opinions, white-collar workers, foremen's unions, public opinion about unions, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 73)
- Economic Security: a Study Outline, 1934 (Box 11, Folder 74)
- Wilson W. Wyatt. Liberal rearm for '48, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 75)
- Art Young. The Socialist primer, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 76)
- Young People's Socialist League. The sixth convention of the Young People's Socialist League of America, 1932 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  July 22-24, 1932.
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations). Your rights under the National Labor Relations Act., 1937 (Box 11, Folder 78)
- Cooks, Countermen, Soda Dispensers, Food Checkers, Cashiers and Assistants Union.. Your union, what it is, how it operates: a message for the new member (Box 11, Folder 79)
- Charles S. Zimmerman. Class approach, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 80)
- Grigory YevseyevichZinovyev. Report. Work of the executive Committee of the Communist International. Fifth congress of the Communist International., 1924 (Box 11, Folder 81)
- Grigory Yevseyevich Zinovyev. Speech in reply to discussion of Report on the work of the E.C.C.I., 1924 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  Delivered by G. Zinoviev, June 26th, 1924. Resolution on the Report of the E.C.C.I.
- Vladimir Ilich Lenin; Ulyanov-Lenin; A. Sirnis. The Collapse of the Second International, 1920 (Box 11, Folder 83)